lostwaldo.com 2018-12-29

# Privacy Policy - LostWaldo

### Introduction

LostWaldo.com is a trading name of Clicksco Digital Limited (together “we”, “us” “our”)  a Jersey corporation. Our representative within the EU in respect of its processing of EU resident data is Clicksco (UK) Limited.  We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting your personal data. This privacy notice will inform you as to how we look after your personal data when you visit our Site (regardless of where you visit it from) and tell you about your data protection rights and how the law protects you.

### **1\. Important information and who we are**

**Purpose of this privacy notice**

This privacy notice aims to give you information on how we collect and process your personal data through your use of this Site, and any data you may provide through this Site including when you request a trial, contact us or service subscribe for news and insights.

This Site is not intended for children and we do not knowingly collect data relating to children.

It is important that you read this privacy notice together with any other privacy notice or fair processing notice we may provide on specific occasions when we are collecting or processing personal data about you so that you are fully aware of how and why we are using your data. This privacy notice supplements the other notices and is not intended to override them.

**Controller**

Clicksco Digital Limited is the controller and responsible for your personal data.

You have the right to make a complaint at any time to the Office of the Information Commission in Jersey or in respect of European Resident personal data the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO), the UK supervisory authority for data protection issues (www.ico.org.uk). We would, however, appreciate the chance to deal with your concerns before you approach either of these organisations so please contact us in the first instance.

**Changes to the privacy notice and your duty to inform us of changes**

Historic versions of this Privacy Policy are archived can be obtained by contacting us.

It is important that the personal data we hold about you is accurate and current. Please keep us informed if your personal data changes during your relationship with us.

**Third-party links**

This Site may include links to third-party Sites, plug-ins and applications. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not control these third-party Sites and are not responsible for their privacy statements. When you

leave our Site, we encourage you to read the privacy notice of every Site you visit.

### 2\. The data we collect about you

Personal data, or personal information, means any information about an individual from which that person can be identified. It does not include data where the identity has been removed (anonymous data).

We may collect, use, store and transfer different kinds of personal data about you which we have grouped together follows:

  * **Identity Data** includes first name, maiden name, last name, username or similar identifier, marital status, title, date of birth and gender.
  * **Contact Data** includes billing address, delivery address, email address and telephone numbers.
  * **Technical Data** includes internet protocol (IP) address, your login data, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform and other technology on the devices you use to access this Site.
  * **Profile Data** includes your username and password, purchases or orders made by you, your interests, preferences, feedback and survey responses.
  * **Usage Data** includes information about how you use our Site, products and services.
  * **Marketing and Communications Data** includes your preferences in receiving marketing from us and our third parties and your communication preferences.

We also collect, use and share **Aggregated Data** such as statistical or demographic data for any purpose. Aggregated Data may be derived from your personal data but is not considered personal data in law as this data does **not** directly or indirectly reveal your identity. For example, we may aggregate your Usage Data to calculate the percentage of users accessing a specific website feature. However, if we combine or connect Aggregated Data with your personal data so that it can directly or indirectly identify you, we treat the combined data as personal data which will be used in accordance with this privacy notice. For more information please see our [_Cookie Policy._](http://www.clicksco.com/cookie)

We do not collect any **Special Categories of Personal Data** about you (this includes details about your race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, sex life, sexual orientation, political opinions, trade union membership, information about your health and genetic and biometric data). Nor do we collect any information about criminal convictions and offences.

**If you fail to provide personal data**

Where we need to collect personal data by law, or under the terms of a contract we have with you and you fail to provide that data when requested, we may not be able to perform the contract we have or are trying to enter into with you (for example, to provide you with goods or services). In this case, we may have to cancel a product or service you have with us but we will notify you if this is the case at the time.

### 3\. How is your personal data collected?

We use different methods to collect data from and about you including through:

  * **Direct interactions** **.** You may give us your Identity and Contact details such as your full name, email address and phone number by filling in forms or by corresponding with us by post, phone, email or otherwise. This includes personal data you provide when you:
  * create an account on our Site;
  * subscribe to our service or publications;
  * request marketing to be sent to you;
  * enter a competition, promotion or survey; or
  * give us some feedback.

  * **Automated technologies or interactions.** As you interact with our Site, we may automatically collect Technical Data about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns. We collect this personal data by using cookies, pixels/beacons and statistical IDs

Please see our [_Cookie Policy_](http://www.clicksco.com/cookies) for further details.

  * **Third parties or publicly available sources.** We may receive personal data about you from various third parties

Purposes for which we will use your personal data

We have set out below, in a table format, a description of all the ways we may use your personal data, and which of the legal bases we rely on to do so. We have also identified what our legitimate interests are where appropriate.

Note that we may process your personal data for more than one lawful ground depending on the specific purpose for which we are using your data. Please contact us if you need details about the specific legal ground we are relying on to process your personal data where more than one ground has been set out in the table below.

**Purpose/Activity** | **Type of data** | **Lawful basis for processing including basis of legitimate interest**  
---|---|---  
To manage our relationship with you which will include: 

(a) Notifying you about changes to our terms or privacy policy

(b) Asking you to leave a review or take a survey

| (a) Identity 

(b) Contact

(c) Profile

(d) Marketing and Communications

| (a) Performance of a contract with you 

(b) Necessary to comply with a legal obligation

(c) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to keep our records updated and to study how customers use our services)  
  
To enable you to partake in a competition or complete a survey | (a) Identity 

(b) Contact

(c) Profile

(d) Usage

(e) Marketing and Communications

| (a) Performance of a contract with you 

(b) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to study how customers use our products/services, to develop them and grow our business)  
  
To administer and protect our business and this Site (including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, system maintenance, support, reporting and hosting of data) | (a) Identity 

(b) Contact

(c) Technical

| (a) Necessary for our legitimate interests (for running our business, provision of administration and IT services, network security, to prevent fraud and in the context of a business reorganisation or group restructuring exercise) 

(b) Necessary to comply with a legal obligation  
  
To deliver relevant Site content and advertisements to you and measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve to you | (a) Identity 

(b) Contact

(c) Profile

(d) Usage

(e) Marketing and Communications

(f) Technical

| Necessary for our legitimate interests (to study how customers use our products/services, to develop them, to grow our business and to inform our marketing strategy)  
To use data analytics to improve our Site, products/services, marketing, customer relationships and experiences | (a) Technical 

(b) Usage

| Necessary for our legitimate interests (to define types of customers for our products and services, to keep our Site updated and relevant, to develop our business and to inform our marketing strategy)  
To make suggestions and recommendations to you about goods or services that may be of interest to you | (a) Identity 

(b) Contact

(c) Technical

(d) Usage

(e) Profile

| Necessary for our legitimate interests (to develop our products/services and grow our business)  
  
**Marketing**

We strive to provide you with choices regarding certain personal data uses, particularly around marketing and advertising. We have established the following personal data control mechanisms:

**Promotional offers from us**

We may use your Identity, Contact, Technical, Usage and Profile Data to form a view on what we think you may want or need, or what may be of interest to you. This is how we decide which products, services and offers may be relevant for you.

You will receive marketing communications from us if you have requested information from us or purchased services from us and, in each case, you have not opted out of receiving that marketing.

**Third-party marketing**

We will get your express opt-in consent before we share your personal data with any company outside the Clicksco group of companies for electronic marketing purposes (including text or email) or by phone.

**Opting out**

You can ask us or third parties to stop sending you marketing messages at any time contacting us at [_data-protection@clicksco.com_](mailto:data-protection@clicksco.com)

Where you opt out of receiving these marketing messages, this will not apply to personal data provided to us as a result of a product/service purchase, warranty registration, product/service experience or other transactions.

**Cookies**

### (a)            On our Site

You can limit the way that we tailor advertising to you on our Sites where this is based on your information by objecting to the cookies that we or third parties wish to place on your browser or deleting the cookies that we or third parties have placed on your browser during your use of our Sites Please see our [_Cookie Policy_](http://www.clicksco.com/cookies) for more details of how to delete these cookies.

### (b)            On third party Sites

You can limit the way that advertising is tailored to you on third party Sites where this is based on your personal information by objecting to the cookies that we or third parties wish to place on your browser or deleting the cookies that we or third parties have placed on your browser during your use of third party Sites. Please see the cookie policy published on the applicable third party Site for more details of how to do this.

After you have exercised your right to object or reject the use of cookies, you may still see advertisements, but the advertising may not be as relevant to your interests. If you change your computer, change your browser or delete certain cookies, you will need to renew your preferences.

**Personalised Advertising**

You may opt-out of future Personalised Advertising on all of our Sites and our Partner Sites by through our [_Cookie Policy_](http://www.clicksco.com/cookies).

### Change of purpose

We will only use your personal data for the purposes for which we collected it, unless we reasonably consider that we need to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible with the original purpose. If you wish to get an explanation as to how the processing for the new purpose is compatible with the original purpose, please contact us.

If we need to use your personal data for an unrelated purpose, we will notify you and we will explain the legal basis which allows us to do so.

Please note that we may process your personal data without your knowledge or consent, in compliance with the above rules, where this is required or permitted by law.

### 4\. Disclosures of your personal data

We may have to share your personal data with the parties set out below for the purposes set out in the table in paragraph 4 above.

  * Internal Third Parties as set out in the _Glossary_.
  * External Third Parties as set out in the _Glossary_.
  * Third parties to whom we may choose to sell, transfer, or merge parts of our business or our assets. Alternatively, we may seek to acquire other businesses or merge with them. If a change happens to our business, then the new owners may use your personal data in the same way as set out in this privacy notice.

We require all third parties to respect the security of your personal data and to treat it in accordance with the law. We do not allow our third-party service providers to use your personal data for their own purposes and only permit them to process your personal data for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions.

### 5\. International transfers

We share your personal data within the Clicksco Group. This will involve transferring your data outside the European Economic Area ( **EEA** ).

Many of our external third parties are based outside the European Economic Area ( **EEA** ) so their processing of your personal data will involve a transfer of data outside the EEA.

Whenever we transfer your personal data out of the EEA, we ensure a similar degree of protection is afforded to it by ensuring at least one of the following safeguards is implemented:

  * We will only transfer your personal data to countries that have been deemed to provide an adequate level of protection for personal data by the European Commission. For further details, see European Commission: Adequacy of the protection of personal data in non-EU countries.
  * Where we use certain service providers, we may use specific contracts approved by the European Commission which give personal data the same protection it has in Europe. For further details, see European Commission: Model contracts for the transfer of personal data to third countries.
  * Where we use providers based in the US, we may transfer data to them if they are part of the Privacy Shield which requires them to provide similar protection to personal data shared between the Europe and the US. For further details, see European Commission: EU-US Privacy Shield.

Please contact us if you want further information on the specific mechanism used by us when transferring your personal data out of the EEA.

### 6\. Data security

We have put in place appropriate security measures to prevent your personal data from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way, altered or disclosed. In addition, we limit access to your personal data to those employees, agents, contractors and other third parties who have a business need to know. They will only process your personal data on our instructions and they are subject to a duty of confidentiality.

We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where an applicable data protection law requires us to do so.

### 7\. Data retention

How long will you use my personal data for?

We will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.

To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.

### 8\. Your legal rights

Under certain circumstances, you have rights under data protection laws in relation to your personal data.

**Request access** to your personal data (commonly known as a “data subject access request”). This enables you to receive a copy of the personal data we hold about you and to check that we are lawfully processing it.

**Request correction** of the personal data that we hold about you. This enables you to have any inaccurate data we hold about you corrected, though we may need to verify the accuracy of the new data you provide to us.

**Request erasure** of your personal data. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove personal data where there is no good reason for us continuing to process it. You also have the right to ask us to delete or remove your personal data where you have successfully exercised your right to object to processing (see below), where we may have processed your information unlawfully or where we are required to erase your personal data to comply with local law. Note, however, that we may not always be able to comply with your request of erasure for specific legal reasons which will be notified to you, if applicable, at the time of your request.

**Object to processing** of your personal data where we are relying on a legitimate interest (or those of a third party) and there is something about your particular situation which makes you want to object to processing on this ground as you feel it impacts on your fundamental rights and freedoms. You also have the right to object where we are processing your personal data for direct marketing purposes. In some cases, we may demonstrate that we have compelling legitimate grounds to process your information which override your rights and freedoms.

**Request restriction of processing** of your personal data. This enables you to ask us to suspend the processing of your personal data in the following scenarios: (a) if you want us to establish the data’s accuracy; (b) where our use of the data is unlawful but you do not want us to erase it; (c) where you need us to hold the data even if we no longer require it as you need it to establish, exercise or defend legal claims; or (d) you have objected to our use of your data but we need to verify whether we have overriding legitimate grounds to use it.

**Request the transfer** of your personal data to you or to a third party. We will provide to you, or a third party you have chosen, your personal data in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format. Note that this right only applies to automated information which you initially provided consent for us to use or where we used the information to perform a contract with you.

**Withdraw consent at any time** where we are relying on consent to process your personal data. However, this will not affect the lawfulness of any processing carried out before you withdraw your consent. If you withdraw your consent, we may not be able to provide certain products or services to you. We will advise you if this is the case at the time you withdraw your consent.

If you wish to exercise any of the rights set out above, please contact us.

No fee usually required

You will not have to pay a fee to access your personal data (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive or excessive. Alternatively, we may refuse to comply with your request in these circumstances.

What we may need from you

We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and ensure your right to access your personal data (or to exercise any of your other rights). This is a security measure to ensure that personal data is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it. We may also contact you to ask you for further information in relation to your request to speed up our response.

Time limit to respond

We try to respond to all legitimate requests within one month. Occasionally it may take us longer than a month if your request is particularly complex or you have made a number of requests. In this case, we will notify you and keep you updated.

### 9\. Glossary

**LAWFUL BASIS**

**Legitimate Interest** means the interest of our business in conducting and managing our business to enable us to give you the best service/product and the best and most secure experience. We make sure we consider and balance any potential impact on you (both positive and negative) and your rights before we process your personal data for our legitimate interests. We do not use your personal data for activities where our interests are overridden by the impact on you (unless we have your consent or are otherwise required or permitted to by law). You can obtain further information about how we assess our legitimate interests against any potential impact on you in respect of specific activities by contacting us.

**Performance of Contract** means processing your data where it is necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are a party or to take steps at your request before entering into such a contract.

**Comply with a legal or regulatory obligation** means processing your personal data where it is necessary for compliance with a legal or regulatory obligation that we are subject to.

**THIRD PARTIES**

Internal Third Parties

Other companies in the Clicksco Group acting as joint controllers or processors and who are based   in the UK, Ireland, Canada and the UAE   and provide administration or marketing services.

External Third Parties

  * Service providers acting as processors who provide IT and system administration services.
  * Service providers acting as processors or joint controllers who provide digital marketing services.
  * Professional advisers acting as processors or joint controllers including lawyers, bankers, auditors and insurers based who provide consultancy, banking, legal, insurance and accounting services.
  * HM Revenue & Customs, regulators and other authorities acting as processors or joint controllers based in the United Kingdom or Jersey who require reporting of processing activities in certain circumstances.
